You're a jerk, Thom.
你真是爛透了， 湯姆
Look Celia, we have to follow our passions;
聽著希莉亞， 我們必須順著我們的感覺走
...you have your robotics, and I
just want to be awesome in space.
... 你熱愛機械工學，
而我只是想去太空中耍帥一下
Why don't you just admit that
you're freaked out by my robot hand?
你為什麼不肯承認你被我的機械手臂嚇壞了？
I'm not freaked out by- it's...
我沒有害怕， 只是...
...alright! Fine!
... 好好好！
I'm freaked out! I have nightmares
that I'm being chased...
我承認 我被嚇傻了！ 我還做惡夢被它追著跑...
...by these giant robotic claws of death...
... 被這些巨大的奪命機器爪子追殺...
"Fourty years later"
Whatever, Thom. We're done.
隨便你怎麼說。 湯姆， 我們之間玩完了
Robot's memory synced and locked!
機器人記憶同步鎖定完成！
This is pretty freaky.
這個挺詭異的
Shouldn't you be down there?
你是不是該下去了吧？
I heard you guys talking last night.
我昨天聽到你們這些傢伙的談話
It's not my fault, you know.
你知道的， 這不是我的錯
Are you ready?
準備好了嗎？
Of course you're ready, you're a rockstar.
你當然準備好了， 你是個搖滾明星嘛
How's it looking, Barley?
情況如何， 貝里？
We should have about ten minutes...
我們應該有10分鐘左右的時間...
Well that's perfect.
好的， 棒極了
We're on in one! All systems go!
Yeah you, go!
一分鐘後開始！ 全部的系統啟動！
對， 你也是， 快點！
Go! Move your asses! Go go go!
快！ 動起來！ 快快快！
I love it! Come on, go!
這個我喜歡！ 拜託， 快！
That's nice.
很好
Nothing to worry about.
沒什麼好擔心的
Thom.
湯姆
There she is.
她在那
Now.
就是現在
You love her.
你是愛她的
She is your passion!
她就是你的熱情
Be tender to her.
溫柔點
Be honest! Eh- be tender.
要誠懇！ 溫柔些
Remind her what love is.
讓她回憶起什麼是愛
...and, action!
... 好， 開演！
Memory overwrite in progress!
記憶覆寫開始！
You're a jerk, Thom!
你真是爛透了， 湯姆！
Ohp- Sorry! Sorry.
噢， 抱歉， 不好意思
Look Celia.
聽著， 希莉亞
We have to follow our passions.
我們必須順著我們的感覺走
You have your robotics...
你熱愛機械工學...
...and I just want to be awesome in space.
... 而我只是想去太空中耍帥一下
Okay, they're coming. Two minutes left!
好的， 它們來了。 還有兩分鐘！
Speed it up, Thom!
快點， 湯姆！
Vivacissimo!
生動一點！
Why don't you just admit that you're
freaked out by my robot hand?
你為什麼不肯承認被我的機械手臂嚇壞了？
Listen Celia, I was young...
聽著， 希莉亞， 我那時還年輕...
...and a dick.
... 只是個小屁孩
But that's no reason to
destroy the world.
但是這不是毀滅這個世界的理由
Why does he do this?
他為啥要這麼說？
We already tried that one!
我們已經試過這個情景了！
Abort!
中止！
Cut!
停！
Whoaaa!
噢啊啊啊！
Nooooo!
不...
You broke my heart.
你傷透了我的心
I know.
我知道
You forgot me on earth.
你把我拋棄在地球上
I know.
我知道
I should just crush you.
我應該把你碎屍萬段
I'm-
對...
I'm sorry.
對不起
Good ad-lib.
說的很自然
Not my fault!
這不是我的錯！
This time.
這次
Quiet on set!
上面安靜點！
We're out of time!
我們沒時間了！
Come on!
快點！
RAAAAAAAAH!
啊...
Memory overwrite, 90%.
記憶覆寫， 90%
Captain! We have to abort!
隊長！ 我們必須放棄了！
The world's changed, Celia...
這個世界已經不一樣了， 希莉亞...
...maybe we can too.
... 或許， 我們也可以改變
Memory overwrite complete!
記憶覆寫完成！
You know.
你知道嗎
There's a lesson to be learned from this.
我們可以從中學到一課
Could'a gone worse.
也是有可能更糟的